Juliana Macedo

julianamacedo.com

in LinkedIn profile

**** 786 493 9208

Profile

Recent graduate from the University of Central Florida and UX/UI and Web Designer with experience building websites using both server-side and client-side languages, producing a diverse range of graphic designs, working on creative app designs, and constructing various other digital media projects while developing the best user experience.

Experience

UX/UI Bootcamp Teaching Assistant

2U, Inc. | Remote | February 2022 - Present

- Ensure students' understanding of UX/UI design and research methods and practices
- Provide additional support to students as a resource for guidance through processes and tools used during projects

Website & Graphic Design Intern

Alston & Bird LLP | Remote | May 2022 – July 2022

- Design and develop creative website to be used internally by Human Resources department
- Build custom theme with a combination of unique graphic designs and branding elements

Website Designer/Manager

Kathy Dobbins Leaders of Tomorrow | Remote | February 2022 – June 2022

- Redesign existing website with web design team to increase awareness of non-profit organization
- Develop branding while improving website performance and overall accessibility

Graphic Designer

Freelance | Remote | August 2020 - January 2022

- Design unique and interesting graphics while meeting the client's exact needs
- Require little guidance when room for creativity is present and capable of adapting to specific styles

Front End Associate

Sprouts Farmers Market | Oviedo, Florida | June 2021 – April 2022

- Process customer orders quickly, accurately, and efficiently, while ensuring satisfaction
- Maintain knowledge of weekly advertisement items, product information and location, and events to communicate to customers

Safe Distancing Supervisor

LAZ Parking | Miami Beach, Florida | May 2020 - November 2020

- Supervise safety distancing teams on Miami Beach to ensure compliance of social distancing protocols as directed by the City of Miami Beach
- Implement effective crowd management protocols and promote public safety

Fulfillment Associate

Target | Orlando, Florida | October 2019 – January 2020

- Pick, sort, and pack guest orders to meet service and ship time standards
- Fastest and most efficient fulfillment associate for multiple weeks

Marlins Park Lead Ambassador

SP Plus Corporation | Miami, Florida | May 2019 - September 2019

- Assist with staffing and organizing for all special events at Marlins Park in Miami
- Major events included over 18,000 attendees

Education

B.A. Digital Media | 3.9 GPA | 2018 – 2022 University of Central Florida | Orlando, FL

Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, React
- UX/UI Design and Research
- Accessible Design
- User-Centered Design, Human Computer Interaction
- Visual Design
- Branding, Marketing
- Verbal, Written, and Visual Communication
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma, Sketch, Miro, InVision
- Asana, Trello
- WordPress, Squarespace
- Google Analytics
- Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel
- Presentation
- Detail-Oriented, Creative Thinker, Organized, Problem Solving, Collaborative, Efficient

Accomplishments

- National Society of Leadership and Success 2019 – 2022
- Dean's List Placement 2019 2022

Languages

- English
- Spanish (Intermediate)

Interests

- Travel Extensive in USA, Europe, and Asia
- Painting
- Cooking and Baking
- Yoga